onestopplus.com 2012-12-31

# Plus Size Clothing | Lingerie | Accessories & Wide Width Shoes for Women | Big & Tall Clothing for Men | OneStopPlus.com

## Privacy & Security

Privacy Policy and Terms of Use Last updated on: 04-10-12

OneStopPlus® is part of the Redcats USA family of companies, which currently includes several different brands. In order to help our customers better understand our policies regarding the collection and use of information as well as our general terms of use, Redcats USA has created one standardized Privacy Policy and Terms of Use that will apply to all our brands. OneStopPlus.com most current Privacy Policy and Terms of Use was revised on April 10, 2012

### Privacy Statement

Your privacy is important to us and we are committed to protecting your privacy. The purpose of this Privacy Policy is to assist you in understanding the type of personal information we may collect from you, how such information may be used, the choices that are available to you concerning the use of your information and your ability to correct or modify the information you have provided us. 

If you have any questions or concerns about our Privacy Policy, you may email us at [PrivacyOfficer@RedcatsUSA.com](mailto:PrivacyOfficer@RedcatsUSA.com). We welcome your feedback and suggestions to help us improve our policies and practices. This Privacy Policy is only applicable to customers in the United States.

### Our Privacy Policy addresses the following:

  * •E.U. – U.S. and Swiss-U.S. Safe Harbor Certification
  * •Who is Redcats USA? 
  * •What Information Does Redcats USA Collect?
  * •How Does Redcats USA Use the Information Collected?
  * •What Information Is Shared And With Whom Is It Shared? 
  * •Does Redcats USA Use Third-Party Advertising?
  * •How Can I Access and Correct Information Collected?
  * •How Can I Opt Out of Receiving Further Communications From RedcatsUSA?  
     How to be Removed from a Paper Catalog Mailing List  
     How to Unsubscribe from Email Marketing List  

  * •Are Redcats USA Division Credit Cards available?
  * •Does Redcats USA Send Unsolicited Promotional E-Mails?
  * •How Does Redcats USA Safeguard the Information Collected?
  * •How Secure is My Online Transaction?
  * •Does Redcats USA Use Cookies?
  * •Does Redcats USA Aggregate Information?
  * •What is Redcats USA‘s Policy with Respect to Data Collection from Children?
  * •Whom Do I Contact If I Have Additional Questions Or Concerns About This Policy?
  * •Links to Other Websites
  * •Policy Changes
  * •Terms of Use  
     Social Media Sites  
     Promotions  
     Mobile Services  
     Taxes  

  * •Terms and Conditions for International Orders

### E.U. – U.S. and Swiss-U.S. Safe Harbor Certification 

The Safe Harbor program is an international data privacy program co-sponsored by the U.S. Department of Commerce and the European Commission. Redcats USA and the following brands in its group of companies have voluntarily certified their adherence to the U.S.-E.U. and the U.S.-Swiss Safe Harbor frameworks for the customer data that they collect: OneStopPlus.com; Sportsmansguide.com; BrylaneHome.com; Roamans.com; Womanwithin.com; Fullbeauty.com; Kingsizedirect.com; Jessicalondon.com; TGW.com and Bargaincatalog.com.

Through these certifications, the RUSA companies have committed to uphold the Safe Harbor principles of Notice, Choice, Onward Transfer, Security, Data Integrity, Access, and Enforcement. You can learn more about those principles and RUSA’s surrounding obligations under the Safe Harbor Certification Program by going to the U.S. Department of Commerce's Safe Harbor website at:[ www.export.gov/safeharbor/.](http://www.export.gov/safeharbor/) You can also view RUSA’s Safe Harbor certification information through that site. If you have questions about RUSA’s Safe Harbor privacy practices or believe that your information has been mismanaged, you can contact RUSA by sending an e-mail to [PrivacyOfficer@RedcatsUSA.com. ](mailto:PrivacyOfficer@RedcatsUSA.com)

### Who is Redcats USA?

Redcats USA, a member of the Redcats Home Shopping Division of the PPR® group, encompasses a group of home shopping brands that offer value-priced home goods, apparel from regular to extended sizes for women and men, and sporting goods. Redcats USA brands include such well-known names as Jessica London®, Woman Within® and Roaman‘s® for women‘s extended size footwear and apparel sizes 12W & up; KingSize ® offering men‘s big & tall apparel from XL to 10XL, shoes to size 18EEEEEE; BrylaneHome®, offering home textile fashions and decorative accessories; BrylaneHome Kitchen®, your source for unusual and hard-to-find kitchen and home essentials, super-efficient gadgets, utensils, state-of-the-art cookware, cleaners, organizers, decorating accessories, bathroom fixer-uppers and much more. Our two outlet sites offer discounts up to 80%. Bargain Catalog Outlet™ and OneStopPlus™ offer a variety of women‘s and men‘s plus-size apparel and home fashions. Redcats USA‘s brand portfolio also contains leading sporting goods divisions such as The Golf Warehouse™, The Sportsman‘s Guide®, Bargain Outfitters® and Baseball Savings.com®. The Golf Warehouse offers golf equipment and accessories. The Sportsman‘s Guide makes available value-priced outdoor gear and general merchandise. Bargain Outfitters offers top quality name brand gear, clothing and footwear. Baseball Savings.com offers baseball equipment, apparel, shoes, accessories and team logos. With this strong family of brands, many of which have been in existence for over 75 years, Redcats USA is one of the leading multi-channel retailers in the United States, and part of an international family of brands that make PPR a world leader in distribution to consumers and businesses. For Redcats USA brands‘ contact information click here.

### What Information Does Redcats USA Collect?

  * Redcats USA collects information you provide to us about yourself to serve your needs. For example, if you place an order, or simply register on our site, you will provide to us your name, address, email address, phone number and credit card or other payment related information. When purchasing age-restricted products you will also be asked for your birth date. Of course, if you are placing an order, you will need to know the product(s) you wish to purchase. Whether you choose to provide us with this information is completely voluntary. If, however, you do not choose to provide such information you may not be able to purchase products from us or access certain services and/or portions of our websites.
  * Redcats USA also collects information you voluntarily submit when participating in one of our various services, promotions, programs or surveys. From your transactions and other interactions with us, we obtain information concerning the specific products or services you purchase or use.
  * Redcats USA also receives information about you from other companies, including, but not limited to information on your creditworthiness for private label credit card offers and products you may be interested in purchasing.

### How Does Redcats USA Use the Information Collected?

Redcats USA uses the information collected as follows: 

  * to process and complete your purchase transactions and provide the services you request; 
  * to send you catalogs and other offerings to you via the mail; 
  * to contact you about the status of your orders; 
  * to identify your product and service preferences, so that you can be informed of new or additional products, services, and promotions that might be of interest to you; 
  * to notify you of product recalls or provide other information concerning products you have purchased; 
  * to improve our merchandise selections, customer service, and overall customer shopping experience; and
  * for third-party advertising as described below Click Here.

### What Information is Shared And With Whom is it Shared?

  * **Redcats USA Family of Brands** : Redcats USA is a family of direct mail catalogers and e-tailers, including, Woman Within, Roaman‘s, Jessica London, KingSize, BrylaneHome, BrylaneHome Kitchen, The Golf Warehouse, The Sportsman‘s Guide and the outlet brands: Bargain Catalog Outlet and One Stop Plus. The parent of Redcats USA Family of companies is the French entity PPR. Individual Redcats USA brands share collected information (for example, postal addresses and telephone numbers) within the Redcats USA family and other entities within the PPR group of companies. Your email address is not shared within Redcats USA family of brands or the PPR group of companies.

  * **Third-Party Offers** : Redcats USA provides information (for example, postal addresses and telephone numbers) to certain outside companies and marketing partners so they can let our customers know about products or services that might be of interest to you. Your email address is not shared with such entities. 

  * **Third-Party Advertising** : see below Click Here.

  * **Legal Disclosures** : if Redcats USA is required to disclose customer information pursuant to lawful requests, such as subpoenas or court orders, in response to law enforcement inquiry or in compliance with applicable laws, Redcats USA will make such disclosure. Redcats USA also reserves the right to share information with legal authorities and other companies for purposes of fraud protection. In the event the ownership of all or a part of a business within the Redcats USA Family were to change, customer information pertinent to that business‘s operations would likely be transferred to, or licensed for use by, the new owner. 

  * **Redcats USA Credit Card Accounts** : we may share your information with the bank that issues Redcats USA division credit card accounts, Comenity Bank. Shared information includes the date of the order, the type of payment, the amount of the order, and similar items. 

If you do not want us to share your personal information within the Redcats USA family of brands, the PPR group of companies and third parties for promotional purposes, you may specify your preferences by Clicking Here.

### Does Redcats USA Use Third-Party Advertising?

We use a third-party advertising company to serve our ads across the Internet and sometimes on this Site. This company collects anonymous (i.e., non-personally identifiable) information about your visits to our Site and your interaction with our products and services in order to serve more relevant ads. These targeted advertisements may appear on our Site or on other websites that you visit. The anonymous information is collected through the use of a pixel tag, which is industry standard technology used by most major websites. No personally identifiable information is collected in this process. If you do not want this company to collect this information, you may opt-out. Opt-ing out will not in any way affect your use of our Site. To opt-out, please click the following links: 

  * Didit:  
 • [Opt-out 1](http://ib.adnxs.com/optout)  
 • [Opt-out 2](http://assets.invitemedia.com/opt-out.html)
  * [Consumer opt-out: All Network Advertising Initiative Participating Networks](http://www.networkadvertising.org/)

### How to Access and Correct Information Collected?

You can update or correct your name, address, telephone number or email address anytime by visiting our websites and clicking on the My Account or Login link at the top of our websites and registering/logging in with your username/email address and password. You can also call, write, fax or email us to access or correct any of this information. See the table below to update your information with any or all of our brands.   

Brand |  Edit Information Online |  Postal Address |  Customer Service Number |  Fax Number  
---|---|---|---|---  
Bargain Catalog Outlet |  Please visit  
My Account on  
[www.bcoutlet.com](http://www.bcoutlet.com/bcoutlet/profile/login.asp) |  BCO   
PO Box 8320 Indianapolis, IN 46283-8320 |  (888) 289-2815 

TDD Hearing Impaired:  
(888) 355-3096

|  (888) 355-3098  
Bargain Outfitters |  N/A |  The Sportsman’s Guide, Inc. 411 Farwell Avenue. South St. Paul, MN 55075 |  (888) 844-0667 |  Not available  
BrylaneHome |  Please visit  
My Account on  
[www.brylanehome.com](http://www.brylanehome.com/Account/AccountIndex.aspx) |  BrylaneHome  
PO Box 8320 Indianapolis, IN 46283-8320 |  (800) 677-0339 

TDD Hearing Impaired:  
(800) 528-5149

|  (800) 528-5152  
BrylaneHome Kitchen |  Please visit  
My Account on  
[www.brylanehome.com](http://www.brylanehome.com/Account/AccountIndex.aspx) |  BrylaneHome Kitchen PO Box 8320 Indianapolis, IN 46283-8320 |  (800) 784-8006 

TDD Hearing Impaired:  
(800) 528-5149

|  (800) 528-5152  
Jessica London |  Please visit  
My Account on  
[www.jessicalondon.com](http://www.jessicalondon.com/jessicalondon/profile/login.asp) |  Jessica London PO Box 8320 Indianapolis, IN 46283-8320 |  (800) 441-1362 

TDD Hearing Impaired:  
(800) 978-8798

|  (800) 448-5767   
KingSize |  Please visit  
My Account on  
[www.kingsizedirect.com](http://www.kingsizedirect.com/kingsizedirect/profile/login.asp) |  KingSize   
PO Box 8320 Indianapolis, IN 46283-8320 |  (800) 677-0249 

TDD Hearing Impaired:  
(800) 682-8095

|  (800) 682-8109  
OneStopPlus |  Please visit  
The “My Info” section on  
[www.onestopplus.com](http://www.onestopplus.com/) |  OneStopPlus   
PO Box 8320 Indianapolis, IN 46283-8320 |  (800) 400-5527  
TDD Hearing Impaired:  
(800) 456-7161  
|  (800) 456-9838  
Roaman’s |  Please visit  
My Account on  
[www.roamans.com](http://www.roamans.com/roamans/profile/login.asp) |  Roaman’s   
PO Box 8320 Indianapolis, IN 46283-8320 |  (800) 677-0229 

TDD Hearing Impaired:  
(800) 274-0260

|  (800) 274-3102  
The Golf Warehouse & BaseballSavings.com |  Please visit the Login section on   
[www.tgw.com](http://www.tgw.com/) |  The Golf Warehouse 8851 East 34th St. North Wichita, KS 67226 |  (888) 838-5551 |  (316) 858-0456  
The Sportsman’s Guide |  N/A |  The Sportsman’s   
Guide, Inc.   
411 Farwell Ave. South St. Paul, MN 55075 |  (888) 844-0667 |  (800) 333-6933  
Woman Within |  Please visit the My Account section on [www.womanwithin.com](http://www.womanwithin.com/Account/Acct_Main.aspx) |  Woman Within,   
PO Box 8320 Indianapolis, IN 46283-8320 |  (800) 677-0216 

TDD Hearing Impaired:  
(800) 456-7161

|  (800) 456-9838   
  
**Any request to update your personal information may take up to 30 days for email requests and up to 60 days for mail and phone requests.**

### How Can I Opt Out of Receiving Further Communications from Redcats USA?

**How to Be Removed from a Paper Catalog Mailing List**  
You can contact us by mail, phone or email at the relevant address or phone number listed on the above table for the specific brand from whom you wish to stop receiving paper catalogs. Please make sure to provide us with your exact name and address or the mailing label from your catalog so that we can identify you correctly.

We will make every effort to implement any choice you make as soon as possible, but you should allow approximately three months for mailing change requests to be fully implemented. Any mailings that you may receive during this time do not reflect your subscription status, and we ask that you please disregard them.

**How to Unsubscribe from an Email Marketing List**  
To be removed from all of the email solicitation lists within the Redcats USA family of companies and to request that your information not be shared with third parties for direct marketing purposes, please Click Here.

You will be removed from receiving future email solicitations, though you will still receive any email solicitations processed before this request was received. Please know that it may take up to 7 days to remove you from our emailing solicitation lists. If you choose to be removed from our emailing solicitation lists you will still continue to receive order and confirmation emails as well as emails relating to your other transactions. We will also no longer share your information with third parties for direct marketing purposes. 

### Are Redcats USA Division Credit Cards Available?

Yes. You can apply for a BrylaneHome (includes BrylaneHome Kitchen), Jessica London, KingSize, Woman Within, Roaman‘s and OneStopPlus, credit card account or a Sportsman‘s Guide Visa® Card account issued by Comenity Bank to receive special offers and participate in exclusive brand benefits. 

### Does Redcats USA Send Unsolicited Promotional Emails?

No. Redcats USA only sends marketing email offers to customers who agree to receive them. Our online order form contains a pre-checked box signifying your consent to receive promotional emails. If you do not wish to receive such emails, please un-check the box

If you are not placing an order and would like to request occasional promotional email offers, notifying you of special deals, web-only offers and product previews, you may sign up for Email Offers on this Site, or call, fax or write us at the addresses listed above, Click Here.

To remove your name from any email offer list, you may click the unsubscribe link in any of our marketing emails you receive, login to the Account Settings under the My Account or Login section of the Site in question and email us that you want to unsubscribe, or contact the Customer Service Center for the specific brand. To remove your name from all our marketing emails, Click Here.

Registered Site users who have purchased from the Site will receive standard order status communications, such as order confirmation, shipping dates, etc. via email at the registered email account the user has designated. Your choice to opt-in or opt-out of promotional emails will not affect the order status and registration service. 

We may offer from time to time referral programs that permit you to submit information about other persons (each "Referred Person"), including, without limitation, email addresses, names, street addresses and other contact information so that they may receive information and/or promotional offers. We will use and store any such information that we collect from you about a Referred Person only to the extent necessary to carry out your request, and we will not use any such information for any other purpose unless the Referred Person consents to the use for such other purpose.

### How Does Redcats USA Safeguard the Information Collected?

Redcats USA protects against unauthorized disclosures by limiting access only to those of our employees who need the information to do their jobs. Redcats USA employees are trained about their responsibility to protect our customers‘ customers‘ privacy. We limit the information we provide to outside companies to only the information we believe is appropriate to enable them to carry out their responsibilities under our contracts or to offer you products and services we think might be of interest to you. We contractually require that the information provided be used only for the specifically authorized purpose and that its confidentiality be maintained. 

### How Secure is My Online Transaction?

It is very secure. We use highly sophisticated technology to ensure that your shopping experience will be safe and secure. We encrypt your personal information, including your name, address, and credit card number when transmitting over the Internet using Secure Socket Layer (SSL) security software. We constantly update our security procedures and enhance our Site to meet the very latest encryption standards. We retain a third party security firm to audit our procedures to ensure compliance with these standards. All of your sensitive information is scrambled before, during and after your order is placed on our Site.

You may notice an unbroken key or a closed lock at the bottom of the page when you enter our "check-out" page. This means that your browser has opened a secure connection with our Site! You can also check by looking at the URL line of your browser. When accessing a secure server, the first characters of the Site address will change from "http" to "https". 

**PLEASE NOTE THAT NORMAL EMAIL (SUCH AS USING CONTACT US OR YOUR HOME EMAIL) IS NOT ENCRYPTED AND THUS IS NOT A SECURE MEANS FOR TRANSMITTING CREDIT CARD INFORMATION OR ANY PERSONAL INFORMATION YOU WISH TO KEEP PRIVATE AND SECURE.**

### Does Redcats USA Use Cookies?

Yes. Redcats USA uses cookies to enhance the browsing and shopping experience on the Redcats USA family of brands‘ websites. Cookies are small files or records that we place on your computer‘scomputer‘s hard drive to collect information about your activities on the Redcats USA siteswebsites. There are absolutely no personally identifiable pieces of information stored anywhere in these files, and they are used solely by Redcats USA to enhance your shopping experience and to allow us to serve you better in the future. These cookies transmit information back to the computers at Redcats USA‘s family of brands; these computers are, generally speaking, the only computers which are authorized to read such information. The information captured makes it possible for us (i) to speed navigation, keep track of items in your shopping cart, and provide you with custom tailored content; (ii) to remember information you gave to us so you don‘tdon‘t have to reenter it each time you visit the Redcats USA siteswebsites; (iii) to monitor the effectiveness of some of our marketing email campaigns; and (iv) to monitor total number of visitors, pages viewed, and the total number of visitors served. 

We use service providers to help gather and analyze information about our customers (anonymous traffic, and from time to time, individual user activity) on our Site. These service providers‘ only role is to help us conduct our business and deliver the most relevant products and services. They are not permitted to use your personally identifiable information for any secondary purpose. 

Most people do not even know that cookies are being placed on their computers when they visit the Redcats USA family of brands‘ websites or most other websites because web browsers are typically set to accept cookies. You can choose to have your browser warn you every time a cookie is being sent to you or you can turn off cookie acceptance altogether. However, if you refuse cookies, you will be unable to order from the Redcats USA websites using the Shopping Cart. You will still be able to browse our selection, but the order process requires that your Web Browser be set to allow cookies. Moreover, by not allowing cookies, your overall Internet browsing experience could be adversely affected. 

### Does Redcats USA Aggregate Information?

Yes. Redcats USA collects non-personal information about how users navigate through our websites. This statistical information is gathered in order to improve the Redcats USA siteswebsites. This information may be shared with Redcats USA affiliates or other outside companies. This aggregated statistical and navigational information does not include individual names, personal data or account information, so it does not identify you or any other customer. 

### What is Redcats USA‘s Policy with Respect to Data Collection from Children?

Redcats USA takes care to protect the privacy and safety of children. Our websites are not directed or targeted to children under the age of 13 and we do not knowingly collect any personal information from children under the age of 13 on our websites. We do not permit anyone under the age of 13 to register with us. If you are under the age of 13, you are welcome to browse our websites. However, you are not permitted to use any features of our siteSite that require the collection of any personally identifiable information. If we learn that we have obtained personal information from a child under the age of 13, we will use reasonable efforts to immediately delete that data from our records. 

### Whom Do I Contact If I Have Additional Questions or Concerns About This Policy?

If you have any questions or concerns about this policy, please contact [PrivacyOfficer@RedcatsUSA.com](mailto:PrivacyOfficer@RedcatsUSA.com)

### Links to Other Websites

Redcats USA occasionally provides links on our websites to other non-affiliated websites to enhance your shopping experience. These other websites operate independently from Redcats USA and will have their own privacy and security policies. We strongly encourage you to review these policies at any website you visit. Redcats USA does not take responsibility for such non-affiliated websites.

### Effective Date and Policy Changes 

Redcats USA may from time to time make changes to its Privacy Policy to reflect changes in its privacy practices. Accordingly, Redcats USA reserves the right to revise or modify this Privacy Policy in whole or in part at any time. We will inform you of any update to our Privacy Policy by posting a notice on our Site. The effective date of the updated policy will be the date posted on the notice. The updated policy shall replace any prior policies and will be applicable to all current and past users of the Site. This Privacy Policy was last updated on April 10, 2012.

### Terms of Use

**PLEASE READ THESE TERMS OF USE CAREFULLY BEFORE USING THIS SITE**  
By using this site, (the "Site"), you signify your agreement to these termsTerms of useUse. If you do not agree to these termsTerms of useUse, please do not use this siteSite. This siteSite is owned and operated by Redcats USA. Redcats USA reservesWe reserve the right, at any time and itsin our sole discretion, to change, modify or otherwise alter these terms and conditionsTerms of Use at any time. Such changes and/or modifications shall become effective immediately upon the posting thereof. Please review the terms and conditions periodically. If any modification is unacceptable to you, your only recourse is to discontinue use of the siteSite. Your continued use of the siteSite following the posting of changes and/or modifications will constitute your acceptance of the revised terms and conditions. 

**RISK OF LOSS**  
All items purchased from Redcats USA are made pursuant to a shipment contract. This means that the risk of loss and the title for such items pass to you upon our delivery to the carrier. 

**ACCEPTABLE USES**  
You may use this Site for legitimate shopping purposes only. You may not harm the Site in any way or otherwise use the Site in any improper manner, including, but not limited to hacking into the Site‘s systems, spoofing or faking email headers or slowing or stopping the functionality of the Site. In the event you register and/or purchase product, you agree to: (a) provide true, accurate, current and complete information about yourself as prompted by the registration form. If you provide any information that is untrue, inaccurate, not current or incomplete, or Redcats USA suspects, for any reason, that such information is untrue, inaccurate, not current or incomplete, Redcats USA, in its sole discretion, has the right to suspend or terminate your account and refuse any and all current or future use of the Site. You will create a password and account designation upon completing the registration process. You are responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of the password and account and for restricting access to your computer, and are fully responsible for all activities that occur under your password or account. If you are under the age of 18, you may use the Site only with involvement of a parent or legal guardian. You agree to (a) immediately notify Redcats USA of any unauthorized use of your password or account or any other breach of security, and (b) ensure that you exit from your account at the end of each session. Redcats USA will not be liable for any loss or damage arising from your failure to comply with this paragraph. Redcats USA reserves the right to refuse service, terminate accounts, remove or edit content, or cancel orders in its sole discretion. **RESTRICTIONS ON USE OF MATERIALS**  
This siteSite contains copyrighted materials, trademarks and other proprietary information, including, but not limited to, text, photos and graphics, the worldwide rights to which are owned by Redcats USA, its related entities, parents and its licensors or licensees. You may not use, copy, publish, upload, post (to a bulletin board or otherwise), transmit, distribute, or modify any contents of this siteSite in any way, except that you may download one copy of such contents on any single computer for your personal, non-commercial use only, provided you do not alter or remove any copyright, trademark, author attribution or other proprietary notices and legends.

**DISCLAIMER**  
THIS SITE AND ANY OTHER SITE THAT LISTS OURSELLS PRODUCTS THAT ARE TO BE SHIPPED BY US, AND ALL MATERIALS CONTAINED ON THIS SITE AND ANY OTHER SITE THAT LISTS OURSELLS PRODUCTS THAT ARE TO BE SHIPPED BY US ARE DISTRIBUTED AND TRANSMITTED ON AN "AS IS" AND "AS AVAILABLE" BASIS, WITHOUT WARRANTIES OF ANY KIND, EITHER EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING, WITHOUT LIMITATION, WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY OR FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE. REDCATS USA DOES NOT WARRANT THAT: (A) THE CONTENTS OF THIS SITE OR ANY OTHER SITE THAT LISTS OUR PRODUCTS (INCLUDING PRICING, DESCRIPTION AND OTHER PRODUCT INFORMATION)SELLS PRODUCTS THAT ARE TO BE SHIPPED BY US WILL BE ACCURATE, RELIABLE, CURRENT OR ERROR-FREE, OR THAT ANY ERRORS IN SUCH CONTENTS WILL BE CORRECTED; OR MISTAKES IN PRICING OR OTHER PRODUCT DETAILS WILL BE HONORED; (B) THAT THIS SITE, ANY OTHER SITE THAT LISTS OURSELLS PRODUCTS THAT ARE TO BE SHIPPED BY US OR THE SERVERS THAT MAKE SUCH SITES AVAILABLE ARE FREE OF VIRUSES OR OTHER HARMFUL COMPONENTS; OR (C) THAT YOUR USE OF THIS SITE OR OTHER SITE THAT LISTS OURSELLS PRODUCTS THAT ARE TO BE SHIPPED BY US WILL BE UNINTERRUPTED. DESPITE OUR BEST EFFORTS, FROM TIME TO TIME ITEMS ON THIS SITE OR ANY OTHER SITE THAT LISTS OURSELLS PRODUCTS THAT ARE TO BE SHIPPED BY US MAY BE MISPRICED. IF AN ITEM’S CORRECT PRICE IS HIGHER THAN THE LISTED PRICE, WE RESERVE THE RIGHT, IN OUR SOLE DISCRETION, TO CANCEL YOUR ORDER AND NOTIFY YOU OF SUCH CANCELLATION. IF A PRODUCT OFFERED ON THIS SITE OR ANY OTHER SITE THAT LISTS OURSELLS PRODUCTS THAT ARE TO BE SHIPPED BY US IS NOT AS DESCRIBED, YOUR SOLE REMEDY IS TO RETURN IT IN UNUSED CONDITION.

**LIMITATION OF LIABILITY**  
UNDER NO CIRCUMSTANCES AND UNDER NO LEGAL THEORY (INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, NEGLIGENCE) SHALL REDCATS USA BE LIABLE TO YOU OR ANY OTHER PERSON FOR ANY DAMAGES, WHETHER DIRECT, INDIRECT, SPECIAL, INCIDENTAL, CONSEQUENTIAL, PUNITIVE OR OTHERWISE THAT RESULT FROM, ARISE OUT OF, OR ARE IN CONNECTION WITH THE USE OF OR ACCESS TO, OR THE INABILITY TO USE OR ACCESS, THIS SITE OR ITS CONTENTS, EVEN IF REDCATS USA HAS BEEN ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES. 

CERTAIN STATE LAWS DO NOT ALLOW LIMITATIONS ON IMPLIED WARRANTIES OR THE EXCLUSION OR LIMITATION OF CERTAIN DAMAGES. IF THESE LAWS APPLY TO YOU, SOME OR ALL OF THE ABOVE DISCLAIMERS, EXCLUSIONS OR LIMITATIONS MAY NOT APPLY TO YOU AND YOU MIGHT HAVE ADDITIONAL RIGHTS. 

**LINKS**  
THIS SITE MAY PROVIDE, OR THIRD PARTIES MAY PROVIDE, LINKS TO OTHER WORLD WIDE WEBSITES OR RESOURCES. BECAUSE REDCATS USA HAS NO CONTROL OVER SUCH SITES AND RESOURCES, YOU ACKNOWLEDGE AND AGREE THAT REDCATS USA IS NOT RESPONSIBLE FOR THE AVAILABILITY OF SUCH EXTERNAL SITES OR RESOURCES, AND DOES NOT ENDORSE AND IS NOT RESPONSIBLE OR LIABLE FOR ANY CONTENT, ADVERTISING, PRODUCTS, OR OTHER MATERIALS ON OR AVAILABLE FROM SUCH SITES OR RESOURCES. YOU FURTHER ACKNOWLEDGE AND AGREE THAT REDCATS USA SHALL NOT BE RESPONSIBLE OR LIABLE, DIRECTLY OR INDIRECTLY, FOR ANY DAMAGE OR LOSS CAUSED OR ALLEGED TO BE CAUSED BY OR IN CONNECTION WITH USE OF OR RELIANCE ON ANY SUCH CONTENT, GOODS OR SERVICES AVAILABLE ON OR THROUGH ANY SUCH SITE OR RESOURCE.

**INDEMNIFICATION**  
You agree to indemnify, defend, and hold harmless, Redcats USA, its affiliates, parents, and their respective officers, directors, employees, agents, licensors, representatives, and third party providers to the siteSite from and against all losses, expenses, damages, and costs, including reasonable attorneys‘ fees, resulting from any violation of this agreement by you. Redcats USA reserves the right to assume, at its sole expense, the exclusive defense and control of any matter subject to indemnification by you, in which event you‘ll fully cooperate with Redcats USA in asserting any available defenses.

**UNSOLICITED SUGGESTIONS AND CUSTOMER SUBMISSIONS**  
Please note that any suggestions, materials, (including, without limitation, images, photographs, videos, and sound recordings), ideas or comments submitted to Redcats USA ("Submitted Materials") shall be deemed as not confidential. You hereby grant Redcats USA an irrevocable and unrestricted license to use, modify, reproduce, transmit, display and distribute such Submitted Materials (other than your name) for any purpose whatsoever, and you represent and warrant to Redcats USA that no such submissions will violate or infringe upon any copyright, trademark, or any other intellectual property or other rights (including but not limited to defamation or invasion of privacy) of any person or entity. All such submissions are subject to the DMCA notice-and-take-down procedure described below. 

Furthermore, a person who accepts a prize as a winner in any Promotion (as defined below), or posts Submitted Materials to any of Redcats USA‘s social media siteswebsites, except where legally prohibited, such person grants permission for Redcats USA and its designees to use his/her name, address (city and state), photograph, voice and/or other likeness and, if applicable, prize information for advertising, trade and promotional purposes without further compensation, in all media now known or hereafter discovered, worldwide in perpetuity, without notice or review or approval. 

**JURISDICTION AND GOVERNING LAW**  
By visiting the Site, you agree that the Federal Arbitration Act, applicable federal law, and the laws of the state of Indiana, without regard to principles of conflict of laws, will govern the Terms of Use, Privacy Policy and any dispute of any sort that might arise between you and us related in any way to your use of the Site. This Site is intended for residents of the United States only. No software from this Site may be downloaded, exported or re-exported in violation of any law including, without limitation, to countries that are subject to U.S. export restrictions.  

**SOCIAL MEDIA SITES**  
These terms apply, in addition to and as part of the Terms of Use and Privacy Policy stated above and below, to users of social media siteswebsites managed by Redcats USA for its brands and hosted by third-party providers (e.g., Facebook.com, Twitter.com, LinkedIn.com, etc.) ("Social Media Hosts"). Redcats USA asks users of its social media siteswebsites to be respectful of the larger community by complying with the terms and policies of each Social Media Host. Redcats USA appreciates and encourages users to contribute comments that are respectful and further discussion on its social media siteswebsites, but asks that users avoid making comments that might be considered: 

  * confrontational;
  * offensive;
  * discriminatory;
  * profane;
  * off-topic;
  * spam (i.e., unsolicited promotion of a third-party business);
  * anonymous; 
  * misleading; or
  * fake.

Redcats USA reserves the right to remove comments or content on its social media siteswebsites that fit into any one of the above categories, or for any other reason, to preserve the integrity of its social media siteswebsites. Redcats USA may block further posting on its social media siteswebsites by any individual who violates these Terms of Use. Redcats USA claims no liability in any way connected to the use of or access to its social media websites.

**PROMOTIONS**  
From time to time, Redcats USA may post a contest, sweepstakes, or other similar promotion ("Promotion") on its social media websites or the Site. Unless otherwise stated in the Official Rules for such Promotions, and, in addition to and as part of the Terms of Use and Privacy Policy stated above and below, by participating in any such Promotion you acknowledge and agree to be bound by the following terms:

  * No purchase necessary to win;
  * Any applicable taxes are to be paid by Promotion winner;
  * Void where prohibited;
  * Eligibility limited to legal residents of the 50 United States and the District of Columbia who are 18 years of age or older;
  * Redcats USA, its parent, affiliates, subsidiaries and advertising and promotion agencies are not eligible to enter or win;
  * Decisions of judges and/or Redcats USA with respect to any aspect of the Promotion are final;
  * Judges, if any, are qualified;
  * Redcats USA is not responsible for lost, late, misdirected, incomplete, inaccurate, delayed, garbled, stolen or illegible entries or postage-due mail;
  * Entries in excess of the stated entry limitations will be void; 
  * Mass entries or mechanical reproductions are void; 
  * Prizes cannot be transferred, redeemed for cash or substituted, except by Redcats USA who reserves the right to substitute a prize of comparable or greater value; 
  * Prizes will not be awarded if Redcats USA does not receive a sufficient number of eligible and qualified entries; 
  * Entries must be original and become the property of Redcats USA upon submission; and 
  * Redcats USA reserves the right to verify eligibility qualifications of any potential winner and such potential winner agrees to cooperate in such verification when asked. 
  * This promotion is in no way sponsored, endorsed or administered by, or associated with, Facebook or any other Social Media Host (as defined above). You understand that you are providing your information to Redcats USA and not to Facebook or any other Social Media Host. The information you provide will only be used for the purposes outlined in Redcats USA‘s Privacy Policy. 

**MOBILE SERVICES**  
Redcats USA may provide certain services that are available to you via your mobile phone or other mobile device if you have subscribed to them, including the ability to use your mobile device to receive and reply to messages from one of Redcats USA‘s brands ("text alerts"), and access certain other features (collectively the "Mobile Services"). The following terms apply, in addition to and as part of the Terms of Use and Privacy Policy stated above and below, to users of the Mobile Services managed by Redcats USA for its brands. 

  * Although Redcats USA may not charge you for these Mobile Services, your mobile carrier‘s normal messaging, data, and other rates and fees will still apply to your use of the Mobile Services. 
  * In addition, downloading, installing, or using certain Mobile Services may be prohibited or restricted by your mobile carrier, and not all Mobile Services may work with all carriers or devices. 
  * Therefore, you are responsible for checking with your mobile carrier to determine if the Mobile Services are available for your mobile devices, what restrictions, if any, may be applicable to your use of the Mobile Services, and how much they will cost you. 
  * By using the Mobile Services, you agree that Redcats USA may communicate with you by SMS, MMS, or other electronic means to your mobile device and that certain information about your usage of the Mobile Services may be communicated to Redcats USA. 
  * In the event you change or deactivate your mobile telephone number, you agree promptly to update your mobile subscription account information to ensure that the messages Redcats USA intends to send to you are not sent to another person who acquires your former mobile telephone number. To discontinue "text alerts" from Woman Within, text "WOMAN STOP" to 73596. To receive help information text "WOMAN HELP" to 73596 or reply "WOMAN HELP" to any Woman Within text alerts. 

**TAXES**  
We do not collect sales or use taxes in all states. For states imposing sales or use taxes, your purchase is subject to use tax unless it is specifically exempt from taxation. Your purchase is not exempt merely because it is made over the Internet or by other remote means. Many states require purchasers to file a sales/use tax return reporting all of the taxable purchases that were not taxed and to pay tax on those purchases. Details of how to file these returns may be found at the websites of your respective taxing authorities.

 **DISPUTES**  
Any dispute relating in any way to your visit to the Site or to the products you purchase through the Site shall be submitted to confidential arbitration in Indianapolis, Indiana, except that to the extent you have in any manner violated or threatened to violate our intellectual property rights, we may seek injunctive or other appropriate relief in any state or federal court in the State of Indiana. You hereby irrevocably consent to, and waive all defenses of lack of personal jurisdiction and forum non conveniens with respect to venue and jurisdiction in the state and federal courts of Indiana and arbitration in Indianapolis, Indiana. Arbitration under these Terms of Use shall be conducted pursuant to the Commercial Arbitration Rules then prevailing at the American Arbitration Association. The arbitrator‘s award shall be final and binding and may be entered as a judgment in any court of competent jurisdiction. To the fullest extent permitted by applicable law, no arbitration under this Agreement shall be joined to an arbitration involving any other party subject to this Agreement, whether through class action proceedings or otherwise. You agree that regardless of any statute or law to the contrary, any claim or cause of action arising out of, related to or connected with the use of the Site or this Agreement must be filed within one (1) year after such claim or cause of action arose or be forever banned.

**TERMINATION**  
All of the Terms of Use are material. Upon any breach by you of any such term, your right to access, download and otherwise use this Site, all materials obtained from this Site and all copies thereof shall immediately terminate.

**OTHER**  
If any of the Terms of Use is unlawful, void, or for any reason unenforceable, then that term shall be deemed severable from the other terms and shall not affect the validity and enforceability of any remaining terms. These Terms of Use constitute the entire agreement between us relating to the subject matter herein. 

**NOTIFYING US OF CLAIMED COPYRIGHT INFRINGEMENT**  
If you wish to notify Redcats USA of an alleged copyright infringement for material posted on our sitethe Site, to be effective, your notice must be a written communication to our designated agent that complies with Section 512(c)(3) of the U.S. Copyright Act. Please consult your legal advisor. Your notice must include substantially the following:

  * A physical or electronic signature of a person authorized to act on behalf of the owner of an exclusive right that is allegedly infringed. 
  * Identification of the copyrighted work claimed to have been infringed, or, if multiple copyrighted works at a single online sitewebsite are covered by a single notification, a representative list of such works at that sitewebsite. 
  * Identification of the material that is claimed to be infringing or to be the subject of infringing activity and that is to be removed or access to which is to be disabled, and information reasonably sufficient to permit us to locate the material. The best method is to provide a URL in the body of an email. 
  * Information reasonably sufficient to permit us to contact the complaining party, such as an address, telephone number, and, if available, an electronic mail address at which the complaining party may be contacted. 
  * A statement that the complaining party has a good faith belief that use of the material in the manner complained of is not authorized by the copyright owner, its agent, or the law. 
  * A statement that the information in the notification is accurate, and under penalty of perjury, that the complaining party is authorized to act on behalf of the owner of an exclusive right that is allegedly infringed. 

Such written notice should be sent to our designated agent as follows: 

DMCA Complaints  
c/o Office of the General Counsel  
Redcats USA  
2300 Southeastern Ave.  
Indianapolis, IN 46201  
Email: [GeneralCounsel@RedcatsUSA.com](mailto:GeneralCounsel@RedcatsUSA.com)  
Please also note that under Section 512(f) any person who knowingly materially misrepresents that material or activity is infringing may be subject to liability.

**COUNTER-NOTIFICATION**  
If you elect to send us a counter-notice, to be effective, your counter-notice must be a written communication to our designated agent that complies with Section 512(g)(3) of the U.S. Copyright Act. Please consult your legal advisor. Your counter-notice must include substantially the following: 

  * A physical or electronic signature of the subscriber. 
  * Identification of the material that has been removed or to which access has been disabled and the location at which the material appeared before it was removed or access to it was disabled. 
  * A statement under penalty of perjury that the subscriber has a good faith belief that the material was removed or disabled as a result of mistake or misidentification of the material to be removed or disabled. 
  * The subscriber‘s name, address, and telephone number, and a statement that the subscriber consents to the jurisdiction of Federal District Court for the judicial district in which the address is located, or if the subscriber‘s address is outside of the United States, for any judicial district in which the service provider may be found, and that the subscriber will accept service of process from the person who provided notification under subsection (c)(1)(C) or an agent of such person. 

Such written notice should be sent to our designated agent as follows: 

DMCA Complaints  
c/o Office of the General Counsel  
Redcats USA  
2300 Southeastern Ave.  
Indianapolis, IN 46201  
Email: [GeneralCounsel@RedcatsUSA.com](mailto:GeneralCounsel@RedcatsUSA.com)  
Please note that under Section 512(f) of the Copyright Act, any person who knowingly materially misrepresents that material or activity was removed or disabled by mistake or misidentification may be subject to liability. Please also be advised that we enforce a policy that provides for the termination in appropriate circumstances of subscribers who are repeat infringers.

### Terms and Conditions for International Orders

When you place an order for delivery outside the United States, the Redcats USA Privacy Policy and Terms of Use posted on our website apply to you **AS MODIFIED** by these Terms and Conditions.

**Placing an Order**  
Redcats USA gladly accepts orders from all around the globe and can ship eligible products to certain countries so long as **the billing address and "ship to" address are the same.** Available product lines, shipping rates and fees may vary depending on the delivery address for your order.

You will be notified at checkout if certain items must be removed due to weight, size (too large to ship in one package) or import/export laws and regulations. You must remove those items from your Shopping Bag before you can proceed to checkout. 

Your order will be completed by our shipping partner, I-PARCEL, who will convert our prices into your preferred currency, collect your payment information and estimate customs fees and import duties based on the country where your order will be delivered (the "destination country"). For international orders, your credit card information is only collected by I-PARCEL and is not shared with or collected by Redcats USA. See the Privacy Policy of [I-PARCEL.](http://www.i-parcel.com/safeharbor.aspx) If required by the destination country, I-PARCEL or its agent may request additional personal identifying information that must be provided to complete the delivery. Such information will only be used for the purpose of processing your order. If you do not agree to these terms and do not provide the information, your order cannot be processed.

Once your order is complete, we will ship your order to I-PARCEL‘s New Jersey location, and then I-PARCEL will ship the order to you. If we are not able to deliver your order, we will attempt to notify you of the problem using the email address you provided during checkout to notify you that your package has been deemed "undeliverable". Please be sure your address and email information is correct during checkout. In the event that we cannot deliver your order (for example, an incomplete or wrong address) your order will be cancelled and we will refund the price of items you ordered. Shipping, handling and import fees and duties will not be refunded.

**Customer Service**  
Email is the easiest way for our international customers to reach us. During our normal [business hours](http://www.onestopplus.com/Help/Help.aspx) you can reach customer service representatives who speak English and Spanish by calling +1 915 225 4970. Other languages are not supported at this time.

**Sizes**  
International size charts are developed based on industry standards and subject to some variability within different garment types.

**Import Duties, Customs Fees and Taxes**  
Your packages may be subject to customs fees and import duties imposed by the country where your package will be delivered (the "destination country"). These charges are always your responsibility. There is no free shipping and handling on international orders, even if such a promotion is available for orders inside the United States.

When you place an order for international delivery, you are the importer of record and must comply with all laws and regulations of the destination country. By placing your order, you authorize I-PARCEL, its employees and agents, to act as your agent with the customs and tax authorities in the destination country, to clear your merchandise, to process and remit your actual import fees for the items ordered. Even if you are ordering something you intend to give as a gift, by ordering, you authorize our shipping partner to act on behalf of the person who will receive the package, and the order must be shipped to your address

By placing your order you agree to allow I-PARCEL to collect estimated duties for the applicable items in your order. These funds will be used, on your behalf, to reimburse I-PARCEL‘s carriers and agents for the import fees that they must pay on your behalf to the appropriate authorities of the destination country. It is possible that Customs clearance procedures can cause a shipment to be delivered beyond our original delivery estimates.

**Payment Methods**  
Available payment methods will be by credit cards and/or through PayPal as displayed on your checkout page. Other options such as deferred billing, gift cards and e-gift cards available in the United States are not available for products shipped to destinations outside the United States.

**Promotional Offering, Product and Shipping Restrictions**  
International orders are not eligible for: 

  * Free shipping
  * Gift certificates, gift cards or e-gift cards
  * Deferred billing
  * Private label and co-branded credit cards
  * Bra Club and OSP Shoppers Club

Certain brands and product lines may not be eligible for international shipping.

Weight restrictions apply and orders may be restricted by size or quantity. Commercial purchases for retail sales are not permitted.

**Returns and Replacements**  
Customer Driven Returns: **(Sales are final after 90 Days)**  
"Your Satisfaction is Guaranteed". If you received the correct item but, for any reason not related to quality, you‘re not satisfied with your purchase, simply return it within **90 days** of receipt for a refund of the purchase amount. **Returns will not be accepted after 90 days.** We recommend that you use a return method that can be insured and tracked as we are not responsible for lost or damaged packages.

If you return a product to us, you will be the exporter from the destination country. You must comply with all the above regulations and requirements and pay applicable duties and taxes. **Shipping and handling, return freight, duties and customs fees on the original shipment are not refundable.** Additionally, you will be responsible for all shipping and handling, export and import fees associated with the return shipment back to our return center in the United States. Title and risk of loss are yours and only transfer to us when we receive the product at our fulfillment centers. For additional information, please [contact us.](http://www.onestopplus.com/Help/Help.aspx)

 _Returns Due to Problems:_

(Quality, Damage, Wrong Item) In the unlikely event we send you an item that has a quality issue, is damaged or is broken, [contact us](http://www.onestopplus.com/Help/Help.aspx), or by calling +1 915 225 4970 to describe the problem. 

**Coupons and Special Offers**  
Promotions are usually limited to residents of the United States. Redcats USA will do its best to ensure that you are only offered promotions that apply to international shipments, so look for that notice on any coupon you may find. "Free Gift" and sale items may be subject to duties, taxes, and import fees. You will be responsible for these charges plus any shipping and handling incurred in getting the goods to the final destination.

**Shipping Times**  
Click here for [shipping options](http://www.onestopplus.com/Help/Help_ShippingHandling.aspx#shipping-handling-methods-del-times)  
Customs clearance procedures may cause delays beyond original delivery estimates.

**Consent**  
By placing an order for delivery outside the United States, you are agreeing to these Terms and Conditions for International Orders and the Redcats USA Privacy Policy and Terms of Use as modified by the Privacy Policy Modifications for International Shipment described below. 

**Privacy Policy Modifications for International Shipments**  
We value and protect your privacy as described in our Privacy Policy, and remind you that international shipments are subject to opening and inspection by customs authorities. When you submit information to us it is collected on a site that encrypts your information. When you send or receive emails about the status of your order using regular internet connections, those messages are not encrypted and you should not include sensitive data such as a credit card number. If you contact us by phone, your call may be monitored or recorded for quality assurance purposes.

We provide certain order, shipment, and product information to our international carriers, so they may discuss your order with customs authorities in order to obtain customs clearance and to comply with applicable laws.

Our Privacy Policy applies to all customers but the specific sections of our Privacy Policy listed below are modified for shipments outside the United States as follows:

**What Information Does Redcats USA Collect?**

  * Some destinations require us to collect special import identification numbers prior to check out. This information is required to process your order through customs and deliver your order, and is used only for that purpose.
  * Redcats USA does not send catalogs or other mailings to international addresses that are not United States territories or possessions.
  * Redcats USA does not collect credit card information related to international orders, and does not obtain information from other companies about your credit worthiness.

**How Does Redcats USA Use the Information Collected?**

  * to notify you about other products or services that might be of interest to you, but only if you agree by checking the appropriate box during your checkout process (see also Third Party Advertising below)

**What Information Is Shared And With Whom Is It Shared?**

  * to our logistics partner I-PARCEL, and I-PARCEL‘‘s authorized international credit card company, in order to process your order and collect all billing and payment information from our international customers.
  * Third Party Offers and Advertising: if you agree to receive email offers during the checkout process, you may receive special offers and promotions that may be of interest to you. See the Privacy Policy for instructions to remove yourself from any marketing emails that you receive. 
  * Redcats USA does not share your information with the bank that issues Redcats USA division credit card accounts (for which non-US residents are not eligible). 

**How Can I Opt Out of Receiving Further Communications from Redcats USA?**  
The section titled _How to Be Removed from a Paper Catalog Mailing List_ does not apply since we do not send catalogs outside the United States.

**Are Redcats USA Division Credit Cards Available?**  
Redcats USA Division Credit Cards are not available outside the United States. 

**Does Redcats USA Send Unsolicited Promotional Emails?**  
No. Unless during checkout you select the box that gives us permission, you will not receive promotional emails from us. If you are not placing an order and would like promotional email offers, click here for [more information](http://www.onestopplus.com/Catalog/email_cat_main_notlggdin.aspx). To remove your name from any email offer list, follow the instructions on our Privacy Policy under this section.

**The following section(s) are added to Redcats USA’s Privacy Policy for shipments to the European Union:**

**Does Redcats USA Participate in the Safe Harbor Program?**

Redcats USA is a participant in the Safe Harbor program developed by the U.S. Department of Commerce and the European Union. We have certified that we adhere to the Safe Harbor Privacy Principles agreed upon by the U.S. and the E.U. For more information about the Safe Harbor and to view our certification, visit the [U.S. Department of Commerce's Safe Harbor Web site](http://www.export.gov/safeharbor/). If you have questions about RUSA’s Safe Harbor privacy practices or believe that your information has been mismanaged, you can contact RUSA by sending an e-mail to [PrivacyOfficer@RedcatsUSA.com.](mailto:PrivacyOfficer@RedcatsUSA.com)

**Effective Date and Policy Changes**

Redcats USA may from time to time make changes to its Terms of Use. Accordingly, Redcats USA reserves the right to revise or modify these Terms of Use in whole or in part at any time. We will inform you of any update to our Terms of Use by posting a notice on our website/s. The effective date of the updated Terms of Use will be the date posted on the notice. The updated Terms of Use shall replace any prior terms and will be applicable to all current and past users of our websites. These Terms of Use were last updated on January 24, 2012.
